Guide to the Hans Bethe papers, ca. 1931-1995
Bethe, Hans papers,
- Series II. Policy
  - Subseries III. Arms Control
    - Op-Ed, 10-6-82, 5-year Plan, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 75)
    - Op-Ed, 11-4-82, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 76)
    - UCS Study on No First Use, 1982, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 77)
    - Bethe, arms race, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 78)
    - No First Use, Gang of 4, 1982, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 79)
    - Meeting on No First Use in England, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 80)
    - AAUW, 17/4/85, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 81)
    - Atlantic Monthly, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 82)
    - Cornell Radio, Strategic Defense Initiative, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 83)
    - Non-Offensive Defense, 1985, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - East-West Security Studies, 1985-1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - ASAT, Gottfried, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Op Ed w/ Bardeen, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Reykjavik summit meeting, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Wash - Airlie House 1986, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Misc. arms control, 1986, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Germany, arms control, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Arms race at sea, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Postol, Carson Mark, Nuclear Weapons, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Spacewatch, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - X-ray Laser Program, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Seeking Security in the 1990's, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Russian Political and Economic, 1988, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Arms control, 1988, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - 1990 Revelations, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Non-proliferation Treaty, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Bethe, Gottfried and McNamara article, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Control of Nuclear Arsenal in Disintegrating Soviet Union, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Russian Embassy Correspondence, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Warhead Safety, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Carnegie Quarterly, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Post-Soviet studies, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Russian Scientists, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Russian weapons scientists, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Soviet Union, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Non-Proliferation, Disarmament Control, 1992, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - LASL reports, 1981-1986 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Misc. Arms Control, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Non-prolif., 1994 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Nuclear / Arms Control, 1982-1996 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - VCC-12 --> 11/20 interface/ Arms Control, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Arms control publications and articles, 1991-1996 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Test Ban, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Kendall, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - FAS, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - FAS Newsletters, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Henry Kendall, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Jeremy Stone: FAS, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Arms control publications, 1997-1999 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Misc arms control, 1985-1999 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - USDA State Dept., (n.d.) (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Dust Clouds, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - ABM, Cornell - AAS - Bell, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Antiballistic Missiles, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Antiballistic Missiles, 1967, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - ABM systems, Bethe and Garwin, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Op-Ed Test Ban, (n.d.) (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - History of Nuclear Policies, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Sidney Drell and Robert Park, articles, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Misc. Non-Proliferation, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Hypothetical Threat, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Bethe SDI Interview, (n.d.) (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - AMB's, 1967-1969 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Postol Seminar, H-bomb and Arms Control, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Gottfried, Arms Control, 1982-1992 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - ABM's, Bethe, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Disarmament, 1962-1976 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Dudley, 1935-1976 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Cornell Executive, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Talk to group of Congressmen, July 16, 1985, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Disarmament and Strategy, 1958-1963 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Military Atom 1970, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings - Test Ban, Russia, Disarmament, 1956-1958 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Donald Kobe, 'A Theory of Catalytic War', 1962 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Humphrey, Arms Control and Nuc. Tests, 1959, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - National Defense Lab Proposal, (n.d.) (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Teller Criticism, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - David Lilienthal, Disarmament, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Detection of Atomic Weapons Testing, 1957-1962 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Disarmament Info, 1962, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1961-1963 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - National Security, Army Library Analytical Survey, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Daedalus, 'Is Disarmament Now Possible', 1960 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Woods Hole Summer Study, Disarmament Agreements, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Civil Defense - 1961, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - FAS Releases and News Letters, 1954-1956 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Congressional Sessions 1 of 7, 1957, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Congressional Sessions 2 of 7, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Congressional Sessions 3 of 7, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Congressional Sessions 4 of 7, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Congressional Sessions 5 of 7, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Congressional Sessions 6 of 7, 1961-1962 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Congressional Sessions 7 of 7, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 26)
- Series III. Consulting
  - Subseries I. General and Arms
    Material for Bethe’s outside consulting work on weapons and other topics. Contracts, expense accounts, etc.
    - ONR Office of Naval Research proposals, papers, 1967-1969 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Naval Research Reviews, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Consulting (general) 1 of 15, misc. research, 1954, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Consulting (general) 2 of 15, misc. research, 1953-1966 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Consulting (general) 3 of 15, misc. research, 1950-1955 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Consulting (general) 4 of 15, misc. research, 1956-1963 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Consulting (general) 5 of 15, misc. research, 1954-1957 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Consulting (general) 6 of 15, misc. research, 1954-1963 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Consulting (general) 7 of 15, misc. research, 1955-1958 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Consulting (general) 8 of 15, misc. research, 1944-1958 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Consulting (general) 9 of 15, misc. research, 1956-1960 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Consulting (general) 10 of 15, misc. research, 1959, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Consulting (general) 11 of 15, misc, research, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Consulting (general) 12 of 15, reports, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Consulting (general) 13 of 15, reports, 1958-1960 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Consulting (general) 14 of 15, reports, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Consulting (general) 15 of 15, reports, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Univ Patents, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Brookhaven National Lab, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Rocket Propulsion, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - E.M. Pulse, (n.d.) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - EMP, 1975-1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Brode, fireball, (n.d.) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Fireball Calc. for Unclassified Paper, (n.d.) (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Fireball and weapons tests, 1957-1959 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Starfish/Checkmate and heavy ion exchange in air, 1957-1967 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Bennett, Bluegill, 1960-1965 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Starfish paper, 1966-1967 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Nuclear Test Detection, 1955-1959 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - AICBM, Notes on Jason etc., (n.d.) (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Bethe, Dyson notes, (n.d.) (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Lincoln slope method notes, (n.d.) (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Paper on Radiation, (n.d.) (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Boyer, lasers, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Misc. notes, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Crystal rectifiers, MIT, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Denaturing U and Pl 1946, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Morrison - Confidential, 1946 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Confidential: reactor development, NEPA, H-bomb, atomic energy, 1947-1957 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Science Advisory Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Decoupling (Geneva Conference), 1959 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Inspection Problems, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Travel Expenses, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Los Alamos Contract, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - ONR Reports, 1955-1968 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Office Supplies & Furn., 1953-1971 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Bethe, AVCO log book, 1956-1966 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - E. E. Salpeter, security investigation, 1956-1969 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - AVCO, 1957-1970 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Dept. of Defense (DSA), 1963-1970 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Office of Science and Technology, Washington, D. C., 1964-1969 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Defense Atomic Support Agency, Wash, D. C., 1965-1969 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Lincoln Laboratory, 1965-1969 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Bethe, Hans A., DSA Information, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - U.S. Atomic Energy Commission, Document Inventory, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Professor C. L. Comar, 1968, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - LASL (Agnew, Bradbury), 1968, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Office Supplies, 1968-1971 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Dr. F. A. Long, Consultant, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - IDA, 1969-1972 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Bethe, misc. security, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Inspections, 1970, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Consultation Hours, 1964-1980 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Security--Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Argonne Vouchers, (n.d.) (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Travel Expenses, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Exxon, travel, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Travel California, LLNL, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Travel California, LLNL, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Future Travel, correspondence, 1985-1997 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - General Electric, TEMPO, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Misc. Consulting Documents, 1954-1991 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Santa Barbara, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Deviations from Thermal Equilibrium in Shock Waves, (n.d.) (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Jason Summery Study, Nuclear Explosions in Over-driven Cavities, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Blast Wave, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Blast Wave Phenomena, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Theory of the Fireball, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Splitting of Terms in Crystals, 1929 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - ONR Contract Work 1 of 7: Shock Front in Gas (, 1946 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - ONR Contract Work 2 of 7: Radioactive Decay, 1949, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - ONR Contract Work 3 of 7: Metals, 1953, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - ONR Contract Work 4 of 7: Nuclear Physics, 1953, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - ONR Contract Work 5 of 7: Deuteron, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - ONR Contract Work 6 of 7: Cosmic Rays, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - ONR Contract Work 7 of 7: Cyclotrons, Synchrotrons, Accelerators, Spectrometer, 1946-1956 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Subseries II. Energy
    This subseries contains Bethe’s consulting and research work on energy. Specifically, it includes correspondence, research, reports and papers related to Bethe’s consulting for the nuclear energy industry. It includes material regarding Los Alamos National Laboratory (LANL), Oak Ridge National Lab, Avco, Argonne National Laboratory (ANL), and other institutions. Topics include reactor safety, Fission-Fusion reactors, fusion hybrids, Breeder reactors (LMFBR), Mirror fusion, Laser isotope separation (LIS), Integral Fast Reactors (IFR), Radkowsky Thorium Fuel/Reactor (RTR), Three-Mile Island (TMI), Operation Fishbowl.and the Nuclear Energy for the Propulsion of Aircraft (NEPA) project.
    - Patent, 1969-1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - SA. Spectroscopy References, excl. my paper., 1970-1979 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Avco Separator. 9j symbos, etc., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Coherent Scattering. Schneiderman, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - fsdp config, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Spectroscopy. My paper, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - SA--General. Early History., 1971-1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Horowitz, '72-4, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Avco: Neutral Atom Bremsstrahlung, 1972-1975 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Exxon N. -- other projects, 1975-1977 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Chirp, (n.d.) (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Chirp, various papers., 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - JNAI work 75-77, Chirp, 1975-1977 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Chang, '76., 1976 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Exxon N. General, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Chang, de Baryshe, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Exxon, not LIS, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - P. Everett, Modes., 1977 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Patent consultation, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Proliferation studies BEFORE Glennan Comm., 1977 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Thick Sample, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Glennan Papers [Laser Isotope Separation], 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Richland Jul 11-12, Aug 20 1979; Also letters, 1977, 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Proliferation Background Material, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Ionization by Electrons, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Exxon Panel. Summary Thoughts., 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Exxon, Meetings, 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - AERL, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Exxon Panel, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - JNAI, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Laser Enrichment Review Panel, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Laser Isotope Reports 1 of 3, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Laser Isotope Reports 2 of 3, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Laser Isotope Reports 3 of 3, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - LIS Evaporation Theory, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Misc AVCO / LIS, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Flusberg, '80, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Flusberg. Summary of Theory of LIS., 1980 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - NAI, Phase Relations, Dec. 80, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Presentation 17 April. Meetg. at DOE., 1980 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - 14 July '80, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - JNAI. Last Meetg. w. DOE (3/3/81), 1981 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Atomic Energy of Canada Limited 1959-1963, 1959-1963 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Contract, 1946-1959 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - International Energy R and D, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Light-water reactor safety, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - LMFBR Fuel (Oak Ridge), 1975 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - LMFBR Oak Ridge Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Reactor safety: Argonne and Battelle, 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Argonne reports, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - USNRC 1, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - USNRC 2, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - General Atomic: Correspondence with de Hoffmann, 1956-1959 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - General Atomic: Other Correspondence, 1956-1965 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - General Atomic: Expense Accounts, 1957-1960 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - General Atomic, 1958-1960 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Los Alamos--Expense Accounts, 1956-1981 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Los Alamos: Correspondence, 1959-1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Los Alamos Lab, Consultant agreement, 1968-1972 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Livermore, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Consultant agreement, Kellogg Radiation Lab, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Greenewalt, Reactor Development, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Consultant Agreements, Detroit Edison, LA, OR, 1950-1953, 1950-1953 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - TVA and TMI accidents, 1975, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Argonne National Lab, TMI, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Argonne, 30 Jan. '80, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Argonne National Lab contract papers, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Argonne National Lab, metal breeder, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - SE2 (1988-1990) 1 of 2, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - SE2 (1988-1990) 2 of 2, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - SE2, Energy Policy, 1988-1996 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Nuclear Constants in Reactor Design, (n.d.) (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Brookhaven National Lab, Visiting Committee, 1953 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Brookhaven National Lab, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Reactor Safety 1 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Reactor Safety 2 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Reactor Safety 3 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Reactor Safety 4 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Reactor Safety 5 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Reactor Safety 6 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Reactor Safety 7 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Reactor Safety 8 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Reactor Safety 9 of 9, 1975-1977 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Fusion Hybrid. Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Fusion Hybrid LLL, 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Fusion Hybrid. My papers and talks, 1979-1981 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Gen. Atomic, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Accelerator Conference and Committee, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Detroit Edison Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Huebotter Review, 1970-1973 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - LMFBR (Breeders), 1970-1973 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Argonne Meeting, 12-14 Feb. 74, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Argonne. Aug 21-22, 1974, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Breeder articles, 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - ANL, 31 Mar 75, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Fast Reactor Safety, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - CRBR [Clinch River Breeder Reactor], 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Mirror Fusion, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Magnetic Fusion Energy Program Review, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Accelerator Breeding, 1977-1978 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Fusion Hybrid other than LLL, 1977-1981 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Fusion Hybrid. ANL, ORNL, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Mirror Fusion, 1978-1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Status of Mirror Fusion Research, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Harrisburg Accident, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - TMI, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Wilson report on Safety, Preparedness, March '80, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - IFR reports (Argonne), 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Energy Policy, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - NDA, Fermi Reactor (1957, 1958) 1 of 2, 1957, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - NDA, Fermi Reactor (1957, 1958) 2 of 2, 1957, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Project Cowboy, 1959-1960 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Reactor Safety Study (1974) 1 of 3, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Reactor Safety Study (1974) 2 of 3, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Reactor Safety Study (1974) 3 of 3, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Thorium Fuel Cycle in Reactors, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Reactor Safety, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - 3-Mile Island, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Fermi Reactor, 1955-1959 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Todorovich, TMI, Reprocessing Law Suits 1 of 8: Cohen, 1975, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Todorovich, TMI, Reprocessing Law Suits 2 of 8: TMI Accident, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Todorovich, TMI, Reprocessing Law Suits 3 of 8: SE2, Energy Problem, 1981, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Todorovich, TMI, Reprocessing Law Suits 4 of 8: SE2 Correspondence, 1980, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Todorovich, TMI, Reprocessing Law Suits 5 of 8: Bethe Papers for SE2, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Todorovich, TMI, Reprocessing Law Suits 6 of 8: SE2, Scientific Forum, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Todorovich, TMI, Reprocessing Law Suits 7 of 8: SE2, Reactor Licensing, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Todorovich, TMI, Reprocessing Law Suits 8 of 8: Legal Proceedings, 1976-1981 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - LASL, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - LASL II, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Pacer, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Detroit Edison Company, 1953-1957 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - APDA, 1953-1958 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Vapor Explosion / Energy, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Fuel-Coolant Interaction, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Fast Reactor Safety, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Oak Ridge National Lab Safety, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Kidder and others. Laser Fusion, 1971-1974 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Wisconsin. Fusion Engineering, 1972-1974 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Lasers/Isotopes, 1972-1976 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Energy. Lewis, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - McNally, Fusion, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Wingspread / my article, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Nuclear Industry, Breeders, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Reactors, econ, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Vapor Lasers, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Laser Isotope Separation, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - LASL. Laser Isotope Separ., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - LIS, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - LIS (LASL), 1977 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Energy/fusion, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Hertzberg, 1970's (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Hertzberg, my calc, 1970's (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Manuscript, Mail, Vlases, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Breeder, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Breeders, Clinch River, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Breeders: correspondence, articles, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Nuclear Power articles, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Info. from Atomic Industrial Forum, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Breeder articles, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Breeder economics, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Breeder Info, Westinghouse, etc., 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Dudley, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Energy (Breeder). Udall Committee, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - GE--San Jose, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Kazman, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Opinions on Breeder, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Kistiakowsky, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous for file, 1975-1978 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Lasers, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - LASL, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - LASL. Organization. LIS., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - IFR, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Oak Ridge Safety Report, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - ANL correspondence and mail reports, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - IFR Concept, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Integral Fast Reactor, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - IF Breeder, 1985-1988 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Reactor Safety, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Atomic Power Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Gen. Atomic Conferences, 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Avco, S.A. Expt 1: Avco SA experiment, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Avco, S.A. Expt 2: Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Avco, S.A. History: JNAI, 1980-1985 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - LANL, 1994, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Fusion Hybrid I: Fusion Breeder Tables, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Fusion Hybrid II: My Talk Colo.--Sandia, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Fusion Hybrid III: Talks, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Reactor Safety Study, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Nuclear Tech, Argonne, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - HTGR co-production reactor, (n.d.) (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Radiation Laboratory Report, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Reactor Safety, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - Energy Panel, Correspondence, list of people, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Misc. breeder material, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - ANL: Nuclear Alternatives, 1977-1979 (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - Breeder reactors, fuel cycles, 1977-1979 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Carter, Ford - Nixon, Breeder and Reprocessing, 1977-1994 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Virginia Beach Panel Discussion, 20 June 1980, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - IFR, 1992, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - IFR, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - IFR, Carbon, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 45)